NATASHA **ADU MOSES**

Web Developer

CONTACT



07802819582



www.linkedin.com/in/natasha-adu1



natasha.adu1@gmail.com



github.com/N-adu

SKILLS

IT SKILLS

- HTML 5
- CSS₃
- **JavaScript**
- **Bootstrap**
- SASS/SCSS
- Git 0

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

- Web Design
- Wire Framing/Mock-ups
- Responsive Design
- **Project Management**
- Administration
- **Customer Service**
- **Data Entry** \bigcirc

TRAINING

MAY 2021

Full Stack Web Development Bootcamp | Cheetah Code Academy, Remote

HIGHLIGHTS: Contributed to the development of a COVID-19 App.

JULY 2020

Develop: Coding | Code Nation, Remote

HIGHLIGHTS: Contributed to a break-out game within a team, using HTML5, CSS3 & **JavaScript**

QUALIFICATION: Level 2 IT User Skills in Open Systems and Enterprise

PERSONAL PROFILE

A degree educated career changer with over ten years of experience in Retail, Business Administration and Customer Services. I am passionate & enthusiastic about starting a new career as a Junior Web Developer and have taken the appropriate steps to gain coding knowledge. Myprevious work experience has equipped me with a range of transferrable skills that I feel would be beneficial in mynew career. I am eager to build upon my new skill set and work towards becoming a fully-fledged Web Developer.

WORK EXPERIENCE

AUG 2020 - | FREELANCE VIRTUAL ASSISTANT ONLINE. REMOTE

- Using freelancing websites to cater for businesses with administration needs
- Managing and optimising paperwork to ensure the smooth running of business operations
- o Maintaining a sharp eye for detail when processing important client data
- Negotiating with clients to offer best possible deal

JUL 2020 – JUL 2020 | TRAINEE SOFTWARE DEVELOPER CODE NATION. REMOTE

- Maximising productivity and project managing using applications such as Trello
- o Researching UX/UI concepts to increase awareness of web design concepts
- o Taking ownership of web design processes by producing mock-ups of potential website plans
- Collaborating with teams to cultivate software that increases user-usability
- Delivering efficient project assistance, as requested by management.

JUN 2019 – DEC 2019 | RECORDS MANAGEMENT (TEMP) MITIE. LONDON

Prioritised workload to complete a project two weeks ahead of planned schedule

- o Itemising and storing documents in accordance with company and Government regulations
- Utilising spreadsheets and company databases to create & maintain documents
- Liaising with and enabling external high-profile clients to access important data where necessary
- o Processing the paperwork of multiple clients simultaneously
- Delivering efficient project assistance, as requested by management.

DEC 2018 - MAY 2019: Employment Gap: Career break to care for sick parent

JUN 2016 – DEC 2018 | OFFICE ADMINISTRATOR **MULIER CARE SOLUTIONS, LONDON**

- o Coordinating office activities and operations to secure efficiency and compliance to company policies
- Maintaining customer relationships through phone and email to increase possibility of future partnership
- Managing diaries, appointments and travel arrangements
- Generating and maintaining filing and other office systems to keep documents organised

JUL 2015 – MAY 2016: employment gap: newly graduated, looking for employment

NATASHA ADU MOSES

Web Developer

SOCIAL MEDIA



https://twitter.com/tashelle_dev



www.linkedin.com/in/natasha-adu1



www.instagram.com/tashelle_dev/

REFERENCES

NAME:

Mr. Paul Foster

POSITION:

Records Management & Vendor Manager

RELATIONSHIP:

Manager

ADDRESS:

MIT IE - Marsh & McLennan Companies 1 Tower Place.

London

EC3R5BU

EMAIL ADDRESS:

paul.foster@mmc.com

NAME:

Mr. Eric Dwamena

POSITION:

Care Services Manager

RELATIONSHIP:

Manager

ADDRESS:

Mulier Care Solutions

Suite 51, The Thames Innovation Centre

2 Veridion Way

Erith

DA18 4AL

EMAIL ADDRESS:

eric@muliercare.com

PERSONAL INFO

DRIVING LICENSE: Full UK License

SEPT 2014 – JUN 2015 | EVENTS COORDINATOR (PLACEMENT) MIDDLESEX UNIVERSITY, LONDON

- o Negotiating with venue owners/managers for best possible deal
- Producing timelines to track progress of event planning process and deliver events within required time frame
- o Researching and sourcing venues that are suitable for themed events
- o Planning events under tight budget restraints

SEPT 2014 – JUL 2014 | BUSINESS CONSULTANT (PLACEMENT) PAUL WAYNE GREGORY, LONDON

Achieved the highest ever grade among Middlesex University students (99%), for my Business Consulting module.

- Analysing business to ensure customer satisfaction and retention of customers
- Conducting research on clients, competitors & consumers using qualitative methods to pinpoint business strengths and weaknesses
- Keeping client informed on research findings & producing recommendations to aid company transformation
- Assessing digital marketing tools, such as companywebsite to appeal to target market.

OCT 2012 - JUN 2015: Employment Gap: Full time student at Middlesex University

CUSTOMER SERVICE ADVISOR

(JUN 2012 - OCT 2012 | MOTHERCARE, LONDON) (OCT 2008 - MAR 2012 | X'POSURE CLOTHING, LONDON) (NOV 2007 - NOV 2008 | B&Q, LONDON)

- Providing consistent, high standards of customer service
- Maintaining a current working knowledge of all products and services
- o Proactively resolving and investigating any issues that arose
- Managing the daily duties of the store and the employees
- Scheduling staff working rotas and ensuring there was appropriate resource to cover periods of high-volume
- o Promoting customer incentives, products and seasonal campaigns

NOV 2004 – OCT 2007 | ADMINISTRATOR

STEP AHEAD, LONDON

- Establishing strong external relationships with organisations to ensure positive customer outcomes were achieved
- Maintaining current and accurate records and data

EDUCATION

OCT 2012 - JUN 2015 | BA(HONS) ARTS MANAGEMENT MIDDLESEX UNIVERSITY, LONDON

Grade: 2.1

SEPT 2006 - JUL 2007 | ACCESS TO HIGHER EDUCATION WALTHAM FOREST COLLEGE, LONDON

SEPT 1999 - JUL 2004 | GCSE QUALIFICATIONS ALBANY SECONDARY SCHOOL, LONDON 8 GCSES (A-C)